that were playing those songs,
right? And I'm sure there are other
aspects of it as well.
I think I ended up with a bit of a
scene, and I think that scene is what
helped me get out of my blue funk and
managed to finish my book. And the
things that helped me with my scene
were that I got more time because
during the pandemic, I was working
from home, and then during the
pandemic I also started to work
from Greece and because there's a
two-hour time difference that meant
that I had four hours in a morning to
write before I actually had to start
my day. Also I got lucky because I
started to swap chapters with somebody
who I vaguely knew who was also
writing a book and we started to send
each other chapters of this book.
And so that is kind of a tiny bit of
a sense. scene. And you know, it's
not Liverpool in the 1960s, but
it's a tiny bit of a scene. And then
it's an interesting question.
How can you improve your scene so
that you can be less stuck with your
book? How can you put
things into your scene?
And time is a classic one.
A brilliant idea made very clear by
Virginia Woolf, where she says to a
bunch of super smart ladies at Girton
College. Yeah, if you're going to
write a book, you need some money
and some time and space brutal but
true right so kind of like how do
you improve your scene so you can
actually do some writing it's an
interesting question and I think I did
it to some degree by accident